{
    "id": "ad7d77f159ae4a3898390c790e5bd153",
    "title": "If Or Unless",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will take the job ……………………… the pay is too low.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6a75e04861b4ba48b091cbe552ccad1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will not buy the house …………………… .. you lower the price.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2882eabb3caf48898e72f1188b252d31"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will not come ……………………… you invite them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b386411a620447778276aa533a829ed6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not lose that belly fat ………………… you do not exercise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "08da929ada0349e089689f5b10eff7f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go for a walk – ………………… you are too tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1920b259010649378ad3647fdb78836c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you stop smoking, you will get cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26290d73ee4e4d74a68c779d0e9dfa5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t be able to do it, …………………. she didn’t help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "798c3c7d1efb4b95a32a43800bf83d65"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will be very upset ………………… .. I don’t wish her on her birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e1fd458f3f0d44c08c8970ba73fefc90"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… .. you give me the keys, I will kill you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55f4e8c7566d4c579a3f94b59e7f2203"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… you don’t leave this place at once, I will call the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "28e44127b9844a5495750032e5f502fa"
        }
    ]
}